# Michelle Smith

2726 Redbud Ln Anderson, Indiana, 46011 (765)606-5922 chellemo23@gmail.com

### Summary

My technical work experience began with PC and laptop repair where I learned the importance of accurate documentation, utilizing resources for learning and protecting client confidentiality.

Since then, I have assumed roles in which I was able to build skills in marketing, project management, collaboration, creative content building, and writing among other job tasks.

As a member of the Eleven Fifty Academy alumni, it is my goal to use the skills I have acquired to build a successful career as a JavaScript developer.

#### Education

DeVry University Enrolled August 2009

Communications in Emerging Media

## **Employment History**

Altex Engineered

Lead Material Handler

January 2017 - September 2017

Lead material handler, responsible for management of resources from the planning stage throughout the build process

Duties included collaborating with company management, supervisors, department leads and assemblers and then assigning tasks to insure a smooth build process

Real Otaku Gamer St. Louis, Missouri

Indie Games Contact Manager

January 2012 - January 2013

Duties included marketing, communications and writing press releases and game reviews

Pink and Deadly Reno, Nevada

Co-Founder/Co-Producer October 2009 - October 2010

Duties included project management, research, news and script writing, interviewing, audio editing and reporting as well as social media management and marketing

Best Buy August 2006 - April 2009

Counter Intelligence Agent

Duties included hardware and software repair and maintenance, checking in computers for repair work, keeping excellent documentation, managing client confidentiality and recommending end to end solutions

#### **Professional Skills**

API

HTML

CSS

Javascript Fundamentals

Git

Github

Firebase deployment

Heroku Deployment

Social Media Management

Marketing

Writing Web Content

Flow management

Collaboration

PC Repair

**Customer Service** 

Project Management

Record Keeping

Audio Editing

**Inventory Control** 

**Staff Training** 

React

Nodejs